http://www.hebridean.co.uk/privacy_statement.php

Contact Us
Hebridean Island Cruises Limited ·  Kintail House · Carleton New Road · Skipton · Yorkshire · BD23 2DE · Tel: 01756 704 704
2020 Cruise Logs
March 2020 cruise logs2nd March - A Taste of the Lower Clyde
Isle of Sanda
European River CruisesLife on boardGenuinely all inclusive cruisesTravel optionsGoing ashore with HebrideanDiningThe faces of HebrideanGuest speakersGrand VoyagesWhat our guests say
Deckplans and cabins
Lido Deck
Panorama Deck
Royal Suite
Select Deck
Deluxe Cabin Twin
Deluxe Single
Premium Suite
Themed Cruises
The Hebrides are home to some of the finest wildlife in the world
Travel with experts
Knowledgeable guides and Guest Speakers on selected themed cruises
Engaging shore visits
‹
›
All Inclusive Cruises
Going Ashore
Dining and Cuisine
Cabins
Hebridean Princess Crew
Website Privacy
This privacy policy sets out how Hebridean Island Cruises Limited uses and protects any information that you give Hebridean Island Cruises Limited when you use this website.
Hebridean Island Cruises Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Hebridean Island Cruises Limited may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 1st, 2018.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Share this page:
View and order our brochures online in just a few easy steps.
Choose a brochure
Request Callback
Click on the button below to provide your telephone number and we will call you.
Our office hours are from Monday to Friday 9am until 6pm. We are closed on Saturdays and Sundays.
Call me back
Mailing List
Sign up to receive all the latest news and offers from Hebridean Island Cruises by email.
Sign up to Mailing List
Image Gallery
